(忆往昔)
牧师Boyle带领你走向光辉时刻
Reverend Buddy Boyle Going For Glowing Hour.
当天使降临
When angels come and knock in.
奉献出的你躯壳吧
Let them all in.
没有人类的许可 天使是无法附身的对吧
Angels can't possess a human without permission,right.
没错
Yep.
所以天使们用这家伙寸照容器吗
So,what?They're using this guy to find vessels.
有一大堆心甘情愿的观众啊
It's a willing audiance.
是谁让Crowley掌握大权的
Who put Crowley in charge.
他可是我们的王
He's the King.
他只是个商人
He's a salesman.
现在
Right now.
咱们来谈谈更朝换代
You and I have to talk about the regime change.
你是我们的了
You're ours.
你这个混蛋恶魔
Your demon ass.
马上就要变成个混蛋人类了
Is going to be a mortal ass.
一眨眼的事儿
It'll be damn quick.
我要怎样
Where do I start.
才能求得宽恕
To even look for forgiveness.
不如从这个开始
How about we start with this.
你变成凡人了吗
You're human.
Zeke
Zeke.
Castiel不能留在这儿
Castiel cannot stay here.
他会把天使们都引到这里的
He'll bring the angels down to all of us.
他能避开天使
He's warded.
但他还是被April找到了
He was warded when April found him.
Castiel有危险
Castiel is in danger.
如果他在这儿
And if he's here.
我就有危险
I am in danger.
等等 你怎么会有危险
Wait,you're in danger.
如果他留下
If he stays.
恐怕我就只能离开了
I'm afraid I'll have no choice but to leave.
Cass 咱们需要谈一谈
Cass can we talk.
你不能留在这儿
You can't stay
(雷克斯福德 爱达荷州)
先生 先生 你在听吗
Sir,sir can you hear me.
麻烦您说点儿什么
Please,please just say something.
你还在吗
Are you still there.
随便说点儿什么 我可以帮你
Keep talking and I can help you through this.
求你了 先生 如果你还在听
Please,sir,if you can hear me.
请别挂断电话
Stay on the phone.
你现在可能很绝望 但是
It may feel hopeless right now but.
你打这个热线是有原因的
But you call the hotline for a reason.
在你内心深处 还是有求生欲望的
There's some part of you that still want to live.
还是知道自杀
Some parts that know suicide.
你是谁
Who are you.
是热线电话里那位女士叫你来的吗
Did the lady from the hotline send you.
不
No.
是你叫我来的
You did.
来击个掌
High five.
早啊 Steve
Morning,Steve.
快递
Mail.
击 个掌
High five.
抱歉 我来晚了
Sorry,I'm late.
我得把孩子送到育儿所
I had to drop the baby off at the daycare.
一路上净是红灯
Then hit every red lights on the way here but.
看来我不需要担心什么
Guess I should've worried.
店面看起来不错
Place looks great.
咖啡杯
Coffee urns.
满的
Full.
牛奶呢
Dairy case.
都装好了
Stocked.
好吧
Okay.
最后一个问题
Steve,last questions.
从前你都去哪儿了
Where have you been all my life.
你跟其他的销售助理不大一样
You're not like the other sales associates.
你有些 不一样的地方
There's something different about you.
我能保证我没有
I can assure you there's not.
我懂
I know these things.
你
You're.
你很特别
You're special.
你的大好消息就是
That's your big news is that.
把预言石翻译成了涂鸦吗
You translated the tablets into doodles.
是楔形文字
It's Cuneiform.
我没办法直接把预言石翻译成英语
I hit a wall translating the tablet into English.
但是我发现了一本古老的手抄本
But I find an ancient codex.
能把天使文翻译成
Linking the angel script to.
古埃兰楔形文字
Proto-Elamite Cuneiform and.
于是我就能把预言石板和笔记
I was able to translate the tablets and the footnotes.
都翻译成古埃兰文 但是它们
Into Elamite which is.
是涂鸦
Doodles.
早就灭绝了
It's extinct.
你能认出这些字吗
Can you read it.
没人能
No one cans.
学者们已经研究好几个世纪了
Scholars have tried for centuries.
所以 这是个死胡同
So,it's an dead end.
不完全是
And not quite.
大多数古埃兰文字都是抽象的
Now,most Proto-Elamite is abstract.
但我从Metatron的笔记里
But I was able to decipher one phrase.
认出了一个词
From Metatron's footnotes.
坠落的天使
Falling angels.
这么说
Okay,so.
那些笔记涉及到了Metatron的咒语
The footnotes refer to Metatron's spell.
有可能
Maybe.
好吧
Okay.
要是我们能翻译出笔记
Well,maybe if we can decipher the footnotes.
也许就能逆转咒语
Then we can reverse the spell.
让那帮长翅膀的混蛋滚回天堂
Punt those wingy dicks back to Heaven.
从哪儿入手
Where do we start.
查资料
Research.
泡泡图书馆
Comb through the library.
看看能不能找到埃兰文的资料
See if you can find anything else on Elamite.
Zimmerman灭绝语言大百科
Zimmerman's Encyclopedia of Extinct Languages.
第一卷 Adai到Adakapa
Volume 1:Adai to Adakapa.
这玩意儿一共多少卷
How many volumes are there.
24卷
24.
别担心 一卷都没丢
Don't worry,we've got them all.
太棒了
Awesome.
太及时了
There's a God.
喂
Hello.
我这儿有个案子
I may have a case for you.
爱达荷州 雷克斯福德市
Four were missing in Rexford Idaho.
有四例失踪人口 疑似死亡
Presumed dead,you know.
尸体很奇特
Body's been released a lovelies.
而且案发现场
And there were reports of.
还发现了一种奇怪的物质
A strange substance at the scenes.
我也很高兴联系上你 Cass
Well,hello to you,too Cass.
你最近怎么样
How are you.
我 很忙
I am busy.
好吧 那你想怎么入手调查
All right,so how do you want to do this.
跟你在现场见 还是我去接你
Want to meet you at the latest scene or want me to pick you up.
我现在很忙
I've got my hands full over here.
我只是
I just.
Cass 你还在吗
Cass,hello.
觉得你想了解一下案情
Thought you'd want to know about the case.
嘿 你确定一切都正
Hey,you sure everything is.
常吗
Kay.
他没说自己在哪儿
So he said nothing about where he is.
也没提他都干了什么是吗
Or what he's been doing.
这可是Cass
This is Cass.
他可从来都不擅长聊天
In case you forgot he's not exactly chatty Cathy.
你也不准备在爱达荷州去见见他吗
And you're not even gonna see him when you're in Idaho.
我说过了 只要天使看见他就像猫看见猫薄荷一样
Like I said,as long as he's on his catnip for angels.
他就要刻意跟咱们保持距离
He's keeping a distance.
所以
So.
这一切有什么意义吗 Dean
Then what's the point,Dean.
这都不算我们管的案子啊
I mean,it's barely even case.
所以我这就上路 去看看他怎么样
That's why I'm gonna go and have a little look see.
我才不会把所有精力都浪费在
And I'm not gonna waste the whole of the menpower.
一堆没用的破烂上
On a big pile of nada.
你就是找借口
In other words,a perfect excuse.
不想查资料
To bail out on research.
被你发现了
You got me.
嘿 Steve
Hey,Steve.
我在储物柜里发现了这个
I found this in the supply closet.
你知道这是谁的吗
Do you know whose it is.
是我的
That's mine.
谢谢
Thanks.
我还在储物格子了发现了一卷睡袋
I also found a roll of sleeping bag on the tool locker.
是的 我想仔细把存货清单都查一遍
Yes I wanted to be thourough with inventory so.
所以上周末加班有点儿晚
I worked late last weekend.
在这儿睡上一觉
Taking a nap here was easier than.
比回家在床上睡方便多了
Going back home to my bed.
当然 我有床 也有家
Which I have,of course,a bed in home.
Steve 你真是太负责任了
Steve,you're so responsible.
我一直没好意思问
I've been afraid to ask.
我不想仗着你是我员工就占你便宜
I don't want to take advantage of you as my employee.
我也不想破坏
And I certainly don't want to jeopardize.
咱们的同事关系
Our working relationship.
但是作为一个单亲妈妈
But as a working single mom,it's.
约会是一件可遇不可求的事情
Hard enough to get a date.
我碰上了一个这么好的男人
Let alone meet a really great guy.
明天晚上我休假
Tomorrow is my night off.
我知道你也休假
And I know you're off too.
所以我在想有没有可能
And I was just wondering if there's any chance.
明晚你有时间吗
That you're free tomorrow night.
当然有
Yes.
非常有
你真好
You're the best.
所以 有四个人失踪
So,four missing.
四个都死了
Four dead.
死亡已经证实了
Just got confirmation.
四个受害者有什么共同的敌人吗
And any common threat you can think of.
Joe的速拨通讯录上有自杀开导热线
Joe in there had a suicide hot line on speed dial.
上一个失踪的女孩
And the gal before him.
生病在家 抽屉里收集的抗忧郁药
Was a shut-in who had enough anti-depressants.
多得能开药店了
In her medicion cabinet to stock a pharmacy.
一号受害者
First victims.
是苏格市的一对夫妻
Maried a couple out of sugar city.
以和谐离婚而出名
Pretty much a walking billboard for no fault divorce.
他们生活上都不是很顺心吗
Were they all basket cases.
如果你让我列出
If you ask me to make a list.
本地最悲观的人
Of this county saddest sacks.
他们四个绝对是打头的
These four will be right on the top.
好吧 四个不开心的受害人
All right,so four unhappy people.
其中一个有自杀倾向
One of them definitely suicidal.
但是你已经排除自杀了
But you've ruled out suicide.
你会需要它们的
You are goona want to put these on.
这看起来像是自杀吗
This look like suicide to you.
血迹吗
Blood.
如果实验结果跟其他前几个一样的话
If the tests come back same as the others.
这是所有东西
It's everything.
血液 皮肤 毛发 指甲 内脏
Blood,skin,hair,nails internal organs.
甚至还有衣料
Even clothing fibres.
就像他们自己钻进了
Like these poor souls,got run to the.
世界上最好的碎木机一样
World's finest wood-chipper.
有没有目击者
What about witnesses.
跟其他案件一样
Same as the rest.
邻居们说有什么 一阵粉红色的光
Neighbors reported some kind of a pink flash.
我们到这儿的时候
By the time we got here.
这就是所有剩下的东西了
All that was left was this.
我们基本都查过了
Yeah,we're almost through texts over here.
什么都没发现
We got nothing.
也许你应该试试打给Morrison教授
Maybe try professor Morrison.
我们联系不上他
Yeah,he's unreachable.
他休假了 去新几内亚
He took a sabbatical to live amongst.
愉快地玩耍了
The Trobrianders of Papus New Guinea.
我们现在陷入了僵局
Needless to say,we are pretty burned.
还有一个人
Well,there's one guy there.
每天都没事干
Who's nothing notify-rested.
你是说Crowley吗
Crowley.
我就是说说
I'm just saying.
把他绑着又不是为了好玩儿
We're not keeping him chained up for the one liners.
值得一试
That's worth a shot I guess.
小心行事
Just be careful all right.
别被他的小伎俩耍了
Don't fall for his quid pro quo crap.
知道了
Noted.
你怎么样
So what about you.
Cass给的线索有什么进展吗
How's Cass's lead panning out.
四个受害人 突然爆炸至死
Four victims suddenly exploded.
我测过电磁场
Now I've tried the EMF.
也找过巫术袋或者硫磺
I've looked for the hex bag,sulfer.
什么都没有
Nada.
人体自燃吗
Spontaneous combustion.
图勒人干的吗
Maybe the Thules.
不不
No,no.
我已经把它们排除了
I already ruled them out.
尸体是蒸发了 不是烧毁了
The bodies were vaporised,weren't burned.
听起来是我们管的案子
That sounds like a real case.
Dean 我应该跟你一起
Dean,I should be there.
不了 没有必要
No,man,that's not nessacary.
不用了 我
No,I.
我自己能搞定
I got this one covered.
他甩了我 Jace
He dumped me,Jace.
在食堂里
In the cafeteria.
当着所有人的面
In front of everyone.
实在是 谁会这么做啊
It's just like,who does that,you know.
为什么不能在Facebook上把我甩了呢
Why can't he just dump me on facebook.
像个正常人那样
Like a normal person.
我完蛋了
I've been destroyed.
无论是社交上还是情感上
Socially and romantically.
完全的失败者
Totaled.
我想钻地洞了 Jace
Just so embarrassed,Jace.
都有心去死了
I'd just die.
我可以帮你
I can help with that.
什么
What.
谢谢
Thanks.
祝您愉快 女士
Good day,ma'am.
还有 祝您好运
And good luck.
我要一包牛肉干 还有薄荷糖
I'll have some beef jerky and a pack of menthols.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doing here.
见到你我也很高兴 Cass
Jeeze,nice to see you too,Cass.
我现在叫Steve
It's Steve,now.
见到你我很惊讶
And you surprised me.
不瞒你说 我也很惊讶
Well,the feeling is mutual.
我知道我们要低调
Man,we had to lay low for the angel threat.
但是 哇哦 你这掩护身份真成功
But...Whoa,this is some cover.
我没有荣光了 你觉得会怎么样
My grace's gone.What did you expect.
你知不知道
Do you have any idea how hard it was.
我坠天的时候有多难 我不仅仅是丢了荣光
When I fell to earth,I didn't just lose my powers.
我
I.
我一无是处了
I am nothing.
现在
Now.
我是销售助理
I'm a sales associate.
- 销售助理啊 - 嘿Steve
- Sales associate - Hey,Steve.
在这儿签下字
You sign here.
我负责存货
I'm responsible for inventory.
出售 还有客户服务
Sales,customer service.
我让这里 谢谢
I keep this place...Thank you.
保持干净整洁的状态
Clean and presentable and.
经理忙的时候
When my manager's busy.
我还会准备吃的
I even prepare the food.
哇 你从
Whoa,so you went from.
天堂里的战士
Fighting heavenly battles.
变成专门加热肉卷的了
To nuking taquitos.
还有墨西哥玉米片
Nachos,too.
我这几周来 都在
I've been politely asking.
很友好的请你送几本好书下来
To reading material for weeks.
你就给我拿来这个啊
This is what you bring me.
- 我不看 - 你到底懂不懂古埃兰语
- Pass - Can you read Elamite or not.
那是我最喜欢的古语
It's by no means,my favourite of the ancient tongues.
- 我是懂 - 能帮我们破解吗
- But yes - Will you help us read it.
我为什么要帮你
Why on earth would I.
因为那晚我也在
Because I was there,that night.
我看到你的人性
I saw what humanity did to you.
不管你喜不喜欢 你心中的某一部分
Like it or not,there's still a little.
不是混蛋
Part of you that's not a douche.
抱歉了 麋鹿 我是个彻头彻尾的混蛋
Sorry moose,to the last drop.
Crowley 你活下来的唯一原因
Crowley,the only reason you're alive.
是因为我哥觉得你有用
Is my brother thought you'd be useful.
目前为止 你什么用都没有
So far you've done Jack.
看来我们要考虑备用计划了
Back to Plan B I guess.
什么备用计划
Which is.
把你送给Abaddon
Give you up to Abaddon.
你以为用那个小贱人就能威胁到我
You think you can threaten me with that hack.
她被愤怒冲晕了头 没有一点儿用处
She's all fury,no finesse.
我还真不确定
I'm not so sure.
上次我们见她的时候 她
Our last encounter with Abaddon,she was.
她挺吓人的
She's pretty terrifying.
比你吓人多了
Scarier than you've been in years.
纸给我
Bring that to me.
这不是你
This is not you,man.
你可是个天使啊 别闹了
You're above this.Come on.
不 Dean 我不是
No,Dean.I'm not.
我没能做好一个天使
I failed to be an angel.
我想做好事 但每次结局都不对
Everything I ever attempted came out wrong.
在这儿
But here.
至少我还有做对的机会
At least I have a shot to getting things right.
我猜你可能看不到 但是
I guess you can't see it,but.
我的工作中有尊严存在
There's a real dignity in what I do.
人类的尊严
A human dignity.
我不想打扰你们 但是有个顾客
Hate to interrupt you guys,but a customer.
在男厕里出了点儿小问题
Had an accident in the men's room.
我就去
I'm on it.
哦对了 今晚
Oh,and tonight.
你7点过来 没问题吧
7 at my place work for you.
没问题
Great.
你真好
You're the best.
这才是真正原因
That's what this is about.
什么
What.
- 那个姑娘 - 不是的 Dean
- The girl - No,Dean.
不是
It's not.
Nora
Nora.
她人很好
She's a very nice woman.
我非常确定 她不想取我性命
I'm pretty she's not a reaper intend on killing me.
她还约我出去
And she's asked me out.
人类是会去约会的 对吧
Going on dates,something humans do,right.
我一般碰不上单身就不约会
My dates usually end when I run out of singles.
对 对 我们都是
But,yeah,yeah,that's something.
会 去 约会的
That...humans...do.
我是Lee Ermey探员
This is Agent Lee Ermey.
我马上就过去
I'll be right there.
又一起凶杀案 在一所高中里
This is another kill,over at the high school.
你来吗
You coming.
我都没有荣光了 去了有什么用
I won't be much use,I don't have my powers.
所以呢 我从来都没有过
So?I've never had powers.
你是猎人
You are a hunter.
你是猎人学徒 记得吗
And you're a hunter-in-training,remember.
是 我记得
Yeah,I remember.
- 你说我很差劲 - 我没说过
- You said I sucked - I didn't say that.
我只是说
I said there was a.
有进步的空间 来吧
You know,a room for improvement.Come on.
好吧 我还有5分钟下班
All right.My shift's over in 5 minutes.
- 约会是在晚些时候 - 这就对了
- My date's not until later - Attaboy.
我去开车
I'll go to get the car.
别急
Not just yet.
我先把卫生间清理了
I have to clean the bathroom.
我们本来在说话
One second,we're talking.
然后她突然
And the next,she just.
没有动静了 之后
Stops and then.
整个食堂里的人都吓呆了
Everyone in the cafeteria,freaks.
大家冲到窗户前 指着窗外
Rushing and pointing out window at.
天啊 真的是她吗
God,could that really be her.
没有人看到其他陌生人出现吗
And nobody saw anybody else at the scene.
不管是男的还是女的 没有不寻常的地方吗
A man or a woman...anything unusual.
你的朋友 有抑郁的迹象吗
Your friend,was she...depressed.
- 什么意思 - 有自杀倾向吗
- Depressed? - Any thoughts of suicide.
没有
No.
她可能有有些不高兴
I mean she's kind of bummed that dick bag Travis.
她的混蛋前男友当着全校的面甩了他
Broke up with her in front of whole school.
- 有些不高兴 - 对
- Kind of bummed - Yeah.
比她考试拿C要不高兴得多
Like more bummed than she got a C on a quiz and.
但没有她父母离婚时那么沮丧
Less bummed than when her parents split up.
就是 不高兴
Kinda...bummed.
失陪
Excuse me.
Cass 怎么了
Cass?What's wrong.
我以前见过
I've seen this before.
什么 在哪儿见过
What?Where.
在天堂
In heaven.
什么意思 是天使干的吗
What,you're saying an angel did this.
不是普通天使
It's no ordinary angel.
Dean 这次太糟了
Dean,this is bad.
非常严重
This is very bad.
在天堂里
On the battlefields...of heaven.
有一级特殊的天使
There was a special class of angel.
叫Rit Zien
The Rit Zien.
天使语中的救济天使
Enochian for hands of mercy.
他们就像医护人员 上战场
They function like medics.They tended to the wounded.
去救受伤的天使 特别是很难好的伤 但是
They healed those who couldn't be healed,but.
对于那种救不回来的重大创伤
For the mortally wounded those who were.
Rit Zien的任务就是毁灭
Past saving,the rit zien's job was to put them down.
就是炸成碎片吗
But the granulated bodies.
这是他们的特殊能力
This was their...special ability.
他们这种毁灭的能力
They had this way of smiting that was so.
很快 很彻底
Quick and so total that it rendered.
甚至都不会有疼痛感
Death virtually painless.
但是他们下手的对象不是受伤的天使
But these aren't wounded angels.
他们都是普通人类
That they are vaporizing.They are people.
你说得对
Right.
我也不知道
I don't know.
Rit Zien尾随痛苦而来
The Rit Zien home in on pain.
痛苦就像是他们的灯塔
It's like a beacon to them.
所以 当此天使坠天以后
So,when this angel fell to earth.
他肯定听到了受害人的痛苦
He heard the victim's cries,their anguish.
就像在天堂能听到天使的痛苦一样
Same to hear the angel in heaven.
他在人间继续曾经在天堂的工作
He's continuing his heavenly work down here.
每次一个受难的凡人
One suffering human at a time.
嗯 但是这个女孩儿没有受苦受难
Yeah,but this last victim was not suffering.
就只是一个冲动的孩子而已
Just a normal moody kid.
但是他刚才来过了
But he just got here.
人类情绪的变幻莫测
The ebb and float human emotion.
Dean 我也来凡间好几年了
Dean...I've been on earth for a few years.
我才刚刚能理解 对他来说
And I've only begun to grasp,to him.
痛苦不会消失
Pain is pain.
那么所有人都有可能是下一个受害者了
So everybody is fair game.
真好 我们得阻止他
All right,well,we got to stop him.
你要阻止他
You have to stop him.
你害怕了
You're scared.
现在不一样了 Dean
It's different now,Dean.
一切都不一样了
Everything feels different.
说得对
You're right.
好吧 那我去追这位
All right,I'll track down this.
变态医生 再干掉他
Kevorkian wanna be,and I'll put him down.
好
Okay.
你别惹麻烦
You stay safe.
去约会
Go on that date,all right.
过正常人的日子
G live a normal life.
好
Okay.
还有事吗
Well.
我需要你载我一程
I need a ride.
好吧
Right.
我答应你
I'll do it.
但是不是无偿的
But I want something in return.
- 你要什么 - 打一通电话
- What's that - A telephone call.
别这样 麋鹿
Come on,moose.
就算是Dahmer(连环杀人案凶手)也有打电话的权利
Even Dahmer got one telephone call.
你真想
Seriously.
让他给Abaddon打电话吗
You wanna let Crowley communicate with Abaddon.
一个地狱之王加上企图篡权的地狱骑士
A king and a power-mad knight of hell isn't enough.
你还嫌不够乱 想组个混种恶魔军团是吗
You wanna throw a demonic team up into mix.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
我是说 我也不相信Crowley 但是
I mean...I don't trust Crowley either,but.
说实话 我觉得他不会和Abaddon合作
I can't honestly see him working with Abaddon.
他恨死她了
He hates her too much.
你自己说的
You said it.
你不相信他
You can't trust him.
我们不一定要相信
We don't have to.
Crowley已经被困住了
Look,Crowley's bound.
我们可以随时挂电话
We can end the call whenever we want.
就算他想给Abaddon泄露什么消息
Even if he wanted to give Abaddon information.
他也没什么好透露的
He has nothing to give her.
他连基地的位置都不知道
He don't even know where the bunker is.
他说他能破解那些文字
He says he can decrypt the translation.
他要是撒谎怎么办
What if he's lying.
这倒是
You're right.
我们需要证据
We'll need proof.
这些怎么解
What are these.
- 材料 - 什么材料
- Ingredients - More specific.
一个 咒语的材料
Ingredients...for a spell.
拿非利人的心 丘比特的弓
Heart of a Nephilim,Cupid's bow.
天使的荣光
Grace of an angel.
剩下的呢
And the rest of them.
电话
Phone call.
等我打了电话 就告诉你们剩下的
You'll get the rest,when I get paid.
现在 你们谁愿意
Now,who's gonna be a dear.
把电话给我啊
And open up a vein.
到了
Okay.
谢谢你 Dean
Thanks Dean.
Cass 等一下
Cass,wait.
我不能就这么让你进去
I can't let you do this.
什么
What.
你就穿这个
You're gonna wear that.
去约会吗
On a date.
我只有这一身
This is all I have,Dean.
好吧
Okay.
马甲脱了
Lose the vest.
- 为什么要 - 脱马甲 快
- What do you - Lose the vest,come on.
这样稍微好一点儿了
That's a little better.All right.
这样才对
There we go.All right.
解扣子
And now your button.
解开几个口子
Why don't you unbutton it.
好
Okay.
等等等 够了够了
That's...that's far enough.
Tony Manero(《周末夜狂热》的男主角)
Tony Manero.
好了 你看起来不错
Yeah,good,all right.
听我说 一定要你给她开门
Listen to me,always open the door for her,okay.
一定要问好多问题
Ask a lot of questions.
女人们就喜欢这个
They like that.
如果她说她想去荷兰
And if she says she's happy to go Dutch.
她一定在撒谎
She's lying.
好了
All right.
去吧 帅哥
Go and get her,tiger.
不错嘛
Nice touch.
你怎么倒车呢 混蛋
What are you doing,jackass.
喂
Hey.
Steve 你能来真是太好了
Steve,I'm so glad you're here.
进来吧
Come in.
我以为我会赶不上呢
I thought I was gonna be late.
- 赶不上什么 - 我的约会
- Late for what - My date.
我要去打保龄球 太难以置信了吧
Bowling,would you believe it.
不过就算是去打保龄球
But,damn if I'm not dressing fancy.
我也要盛装
Even for bowling.
自从Tanya出生以来 我都一直没机会穿
Haven't had an excuse to doll up since Tanya was born.
来看看我的小天使
There she is,my little angel.
我已经喂过她了
Now she's already been fed.
我估计她会一直睡下去
She'll probably sleep the whole time.
反正我只出去几个小时
And I'll only be gone for a couple of hours.
我平时用的保姆过不来
I just couldn't get my usual sitter and.
万一她醒过来哭泣的话
I need somebody here in case.
我需要有人在家看着她
She wakes up and starts crying.
不过我保证她不会的
Which she won't,I promise.
Tanya从来不哭
Baby Tanya never cries.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
还有谢谢你 你真是个好人
And thank you,you really are the best.
看孩子啊
Babysitting.
不行 不行
A-bup-bup.
怎么了
What.
不要你的 要他的
Not yours,his.
这有什么区别吗
What difference does it make.
我用过你的了
I've had yours.
我都已经被困在这儿了
Stuck in here.
在饮食上要求点儿花样不算过分吧
Can't fault me for wanting a little variety.
不可能
No way.
怎么了 小朋友
What's wrong,short round.
难道你害怕针头吗
Afraid of needles.
不 只是我个人的原则是
No,I just have policy not giving blood.
不给杀了我母亲的人提供血液
To anyone who's murdered my mother.
我有的是时间
I have nothing but time.
你个混蛋
You're a dick.
祝你们翻译顺利
Good luck with that translation.
咒语
Spells.
我是Crowley
This is Crowley.
帮我接 是Crowley
Connect me to…Crowley.
信号不大好
Bad connection.
Crowley 你们的王
Crowley,your king.
如果你现在不给我接Abaddon
If you don't connect me to Abaddon right away.
我就不得不
I'll be forced to.
怎么了 发生什么了
What,what happened.
他们让我等一下
I've been placed on hold.
你好
Hello.
呃
Um.
别 别哭
Please,please don't.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay,
我给你唱个摇篮曲吧
How about a lullaby.
好了 嘘 嘘
Okay,shh,shh.
看看我身上都发生了什么
Look at what's happening to me.
连我自己都不敢相信
I can't believe it myself.
忽然之间我坐在云端
Suddenly I'm on top of the world.
忽然之间又变成了普通人
Suddenly I'm somebody else.
哦 不管你信不信
Oh,believe it or not.
我现在感觉很开心
I'm walking on air.
我从没想过自己会如此自由
I never thought I would be so free.
支起翅膀飞向远方 一路歌唱
Flying away on a wing and a prayer.
哦 那人会是谁
Oh,who could it be.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not.
这就是我
It's just me.
不管你信不信
Believe it or not.
这就是我
It's just me.
探长
Sheriff.
有个好消息
Here's a wrinkle.
第一个犯罪现场 那对夫妇的死亡现场
Our first crime scene,married couple.
我们刚从实验室那边获得了化验结果
Full analysis of the spray just came from the lab.
现场只有那妻子的DNA
Turns out it only contains the wife's DNA.
那就是说那丈夫还活着
The husband's still out there.
没人告诉过你
Nobody told you.
也没人解释过
Nobody explained.
你就这么
You just shoved out.
连哭带喊的诞生在这世界里
Kicking and screaming into this human life without.
也不知道为什么你会感觉到你所感觉的一切
Any idea why any of you feels the way you feel.
也不知道为什么会有那么多困惑
Or why this confusion.
感觉就像是
It just feels like it's a hair's breadth from.
恐惧 或者痛苦
Terror,or pain.
就当你以为你明白一切了的时候
You know,just when you think you do understand.
结果发现你还是什么都不懂
It'll turned out you were wrong.
你什么也不明白
You didn't understand anything at all.
事实就是这样的
This is just how it is when you're new at this.
其实就在不久之前
You know,it wasn't that long ago.
我只要轻触一下你的额头
All I need to do to ease your pain is.
就会解除你的痛苦
Is touch you.
你的温度有点高啊
You're very warm.
这正常吗
Is that normal.
嘘 嘘
Shh,shh.
他差点儿就精神失常了
He's already a bit screwy.
但他又找到了信仰
But then he found religion.
她是个绝对的无神论者
She was a hard line atheist no peach herself.
当他对那个愚蠢的Boyle牧师表现出极大的兴趣后
When he got himself obsessed with this Buddy Boyle wackjob.
本来就很糟的婚姻变得愈发不可收拾
An already bad marriage got worse.
不断告诫她要相信上帝的存在
Kept telling her to let God in.
牧师Boyle 这就解释的通了
Buddy Boyle,that explains it.
解释了什么
Explains what.
没什么
Never mind.
这是他的车吗
Was that his truck.
对
Yeah.
Cass
Cass.
Nora 她发烧了
Nora,she's really hot.
请给我回电话
Please just call,call back.
如果你不回电话
If I don't hear back.
我就带她去医院了
I'm taking her to the hospital.
好吧 Tanya 我们出去走走
Okay,Tanya,we're taking a little walk.
你好 Castiel
Hello,Castiel.
可悲的小傻瓜
Squalid little dump.
怪不得她要哭啊
No wonder she cries.
她发烧了而已 Ephraim 她会好的
It's a fever,Ephraim.It'll pass.
你记得我的名字呢
You remember my name.
我们见面的时候 我还什么都不是呢
I was just nobody when we met.
但是你那时候已经是个传奇人物了
But you,you were a legend.
你以前就来过这里
You've been here before.
我是头一次来人类的世界
This is my first time.
它很
And it's.
很令人紧张
It's intense.
一开始对人性
You know there is a lot you don't.
你肯定有很多不明白的地方
Understand about humanity at first.
如果你能停下来
If you just stop.
停下
Stop.
我不会停下的
I won't stop.
直到我把这个星球上所有的痛苦清除干净
Until I wash the planet clean of all suffering.
让我来吧
Allow me.
别碰她
Don't touch her.
你以为我是为她而来的
You think I came for her.
不 Castiel
No,Castiel.
我为你而来
I came for you.
接通恶魔电话需要多久
How long will it take to transfer demonic phone call.
别吵 鹿鹿
Can it,moose.
Crowley 你也打了电话了
Crowley,you got your call.
是啊 是时候了
Yeah,It's time.
我说是时候了的时候 才是时候了
It's time when I bloody well say it's time.
你好 Abadon
Hello Abadon.
Crowley
Crowley.
你最近还好吗
How in the hell are you.
这么多的痛苦和绝望
So much pain and despair.
这么多声音
So many voices.
乞求着解脱
Begging out for relief.
你是怎么找到我的
How did you find me.
因为你避开天使了吗
Because you are warded.
和我找到其他病人的方法一样
The same way I found all my patients.
我只是跟着你痛苦的声音
I just followed the sound of your pain.
你不知道那有多大声
You have no idea how loud it is.
我在几里之外就能听到
I can hear you from miles.
你真的以为
You really you think.
你在这里做天堂的工作吗
You are doing heaven's work down here.
我知道我是的
I know I am.
你错了
Well,you are wrong.
地球有时是个很难生存的地方
Earth can be a hard place.
这些人类 他们可以变得更好
These humans,they can get better.
他们只是在尽力而为
They are just doing the best they can.
这就是你认为你在做的事吗 Castiel
Is that what you think you are doing,Castiel.
尽力而为
The best you can.
很抱歉
Well,I'm sorry.
但如果这就是著名的Castiel的尽力而为
But if this is the best of the famed Castiel can do.
你的处境比我想象的还要狼狈
You are a more urgent case than I thought.
我曾经崇拜你
I used to admire you.
你失败的的次数远超过你成功的次数
You failed more often than you succeeded.
但至少你曾经是做大事的
But at least you played big.
而现在你在做什么
Now what are you doing.
把头埋在沙子里
Burying your head in the sand.
在你的族人最需要你的时候
Right when your kind need you most.
数量怎么样
How are the numbers.
你是说灵魂数量吗
You mean souls.
比你预想的要多一倍
I've managed a double on your projections.
我是怎么能 成功的
Now,how did I ever pull off such a feat.
你在提前收取灵魂
You are taking souls before their time.
取消我的契约
Voiding my contracts.
是的
That's right.
我正在把它们销毁掉
I'm taking it all down.
一点一点
Brick by brick.
已经结束了
It's over.
Crowley 官僚主义之王 的日子
The days of Crowley,the king of bureaucrat.
已经结束了
Are done.
马上就好了
It'll be over soon.
我会把疼痛带走
I'll take the pain away.
我想活着
I want to live.
但是以什么身份呢 Castiel
But as what,Castiel.
作为天使
As an angel.
还是人类
Or a man.
你这个
You.
肮脏
Ganky.
恶心的
Putrescent.
婊子
Skanger.
我的效率在你看来可能不值一提
It may look like bean-counting to you.
可能缺少技巧
May lack a certain adolescent flair.
但我的方法奏效
But my way works.
你以为你能控制地狱
You think you can control hell.
就以这么混乱的方式
With chaos alone.
不用支持 来自
Without the the support of those.
依然忠于我的人
Who are still loyal to me.
已经有一周没人看见你了
No one's seen you in weeks.
我最后一次见你的时候
And the last I saw you,Howdy and Doody had you.
你正被两兄弟好好地绑着
Tied up nice and tight.
好像 把你变成哈巴狗了
Seems to reason,they've turned you into a kennel dog.
感觉怎么样啊 Crowley
How does it feel Crowley.
当了Winchester的婊子
To be the Winchesters' bitch.
听着你在这儿虚张声势 还真是有趣
It's been fun indulging in your bluffs.
但是你我都知道 你已经没有权威了
But we both know you have no real authority left.
也没有筹码
No leverage.
你没什么能提供给我的
You have nothing to offer me.
你一无所有
You have nothing.
你的方法
Your way.
迟早会遭到反噬
Will backfire.
等死吧
You will burn.
我等不及了
I can't wait.
Crowley
Crowley.
把埃兰文给我
Give me the translations.
我履行我的合约
I keep my agreements.
取得原料
Obtain the ingrdients.
心脏 弓 荣光
Heart,bow,grace.
等等
Blah blah blah.
混合 直到有烟从灰烬中升起
Mix until the smoke shall rise from the ashes.
将天使驱逐出天堂
Casting the angels from heaven.
等等
Blah blah blah.
哦 不可逆转
Oh,It's irreversible.
什么
What.
这个咒语无法被逆转
The spell can't be undone.
新世界已经降临
The new world order.
我们只能受着了
We're stuck with it.
你说你想活着
You say you want to live.
但是我能看到 你看不到的
But you can't see what I see.
选择一个人类的生命
By choosing a human life.
你已经放弃了
You've already given up.
你选择了死亡
You chose death.
不可能
There is no way.
Crowley在撒谎
Crowley is lying.
不 Dean 这次没有
No,Dean,not this time.
Metetron让这个咒语经得起
Metetron built the spell to withstand.
任何让其逆转的尝试
Any attempt to reverse it.
无法再把天使放回天堂了
There is no putting the angels back in heaven.
结束了
It's done.
你会告诉Cass吗
You gonna tell Cass.
很抱歉我反应过度了
I'm sorry I overreacted.
我的朋友给了我一个小窍门
My friend gave me a tip.
少量的醋氨酚能快速退烧
A low dose of acetaminophen brought the fever right down.
没关系
That's okay.
我的约会本来就是个灾难
Date was a bust anyway.
Steve
Steve.
你说你反应过度
The part of you that overreacted.
是因为你在意
That care so much.
正是如此 才让你如此特别
That's what makes you special.
我得挂了
I got to go.
准备去哪儿啊 Cass
Where to,Cass.
听着 Cass 在基地里
Listen Cass,back at the bunker.
我 很抱歉我把你赶走了
I...Sorry I told to go.
我知道你过得很不容易
I know it's been hard on you.
你只剩自己一个人
You know,on your own.
但你适应了
The way you are adapting.
我为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
谢谢你 Dean
Thank you,Dean.
但是就像Ephraim说的
But there is something Ephraim said.
天使们 他们需要帮助
The angels,they need help.
难道我真的能坐视不理
Can I really sit this out.
难道我不该寻找让他们回家的途径吗
Shouldn't I be searching for a way to get them home.
我和Sam会处理天使的事
Me and Sam will take care of the angels.
你现在是人类了
You are human now.
这不再是你的问题了
It's not your problem anymore.
流星雨已经过去几周了
It's been weeks since the massive meteor storm.
但是爱达荷州的天文学家
Yet Idaho falls astronomers still.
还没有给出答复
Have unanswered questions.
华盛顿当局和航天局
NASA and Washington are both continuing.
将继续研究这一现象
To study the phenomenon